

# SABRINA D TELIS

Graphic Designer

- 813-624-4884
- sabrinadelilaarts@gmail.com
- 1320 Pasadena Bloom Lane, Ruskin FL 33570

## **EDUCATION**

Associate in Arts Hillsborough Community College 2023

Graphic Design Certification Hillsborough Community College 2023

**PTK Honors Society** 4.0 GPA

#### **EXPERTISE**

- Graphic Design
- Illustration
- UI & UX Design
- Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign & Lightroom
- Figma

#### **ROLES & AWARDS**

- President of HCC Art Club 2023
- PTK All-Florida Academic Team
- 49th & 50th Annual HCC Student Juried Art Exhibition
- Art Ascent magazine Artists of Abstract | 2020 Aug edition

#### **ABOUT ME**

Accomplished freelance graphic designer with 4 years of experience. Published illustrations in books, magazines & marketing content. Many years of experience in customer service therefore skilled in a fast pace environment. Looking for a company that aligns with strong values and passion for creativity. A team player and always willing to help others. Dedicated to learning new skills to implement and always seeking ways to expand expertise.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

**Q** 2019 - Present Sabrina Delila Arts I Apollo Beach, FL

## Freelance Graphic Designer & Illustrator

Matching with clients in need of illustration or design. Illustrated the cover and chapter images for Heaven's Bell by Sherrie Barch available in Barnes & Noble & Amazon as well as their marketing images. Designing logos and branding guides for local companies. Creating personalized family & memorial portraits.

2015 - 2019

Laser Spine Institute | Tampa, FL

# MRI Administrative Specialist

Contacted imaging facilities to obtain medical records for our patients via phone, email, and faxing requests. Data input into Salesforce. Created and implemented a Standard Operating Procedure manual for new hires. Remote with monthly in-office meetings and team buildings.

2014 - 2015

The Disney Store | Brandon, FL

#### Cast Member

Created a magical and fun environment for guests. Cash register experience and incoming calls. Stocking shelves and unpacking new products. Participated in Disney's

## REFERENCES

Phone: (815) 494-6496

Sherrie Barch Omar Richardson Heaven's Bell

O Richardson Design

Phone: (912)-604-2070 Email: sherbarchegmail.com Email: orichardson3ehccfl.edu

Christopher Weeks Professor of Art

Phone: (813) 253-7783 Email: cweeks@hccfl.edu